

**FULL STACK WEB DEV** 

#### CONTACT

0478 416 800 adrian.mancuso@gmail.com linkedin: /adrian-mancuso/ github: adrianmancuso

### PROFILE

I'm an avid record collector, modular synth geek and talented full stack developer who enjoys problem solving and adapting to change. I have played in bands in Japan and worked as a DJ in Poland. I discovered my love of programming through tidalCycles, a Haskell based real-time coding language. My passion for problem solving and flexible nature means that I pick up new technologies and develop quickly. When I'm not neck deep in code (or stackoverflow) I like to make bread.

#### RECENT PROJECTS

## RETURN WINDOW FULL STACK

Rails app which allows users to enter clothing purchases and accesses the app's API to generate a Google Calendar notification when the returns window is set to cease.

- -Ruby on Rails
- Web Crawler (Mechanize)
- Web Scraper (Nokogiri)
- -Google Calendar API

## 'MAN' WEBSITE 31HR HACKATHON ENTRY

Project brief was to create a resource to proactively battle factors which contribute to male suicide in the 14-46 age group.

- -Developed a website which connected users to a mentor in their field of interest for a regular meetups
- -Hackathon organisers have since contacted myself and my partner for future work
- -Cross disciplinary team (3 UX designers and 2 developers)
- -Bootstrapped front end as per UX specifications
- -Back end tech included Ruby, PostgreSQL

## WOOFER - TINDER FOR DOGS FULL STACK

RESTful, tongue in cheek social network for lonely dogs to connect to others in their vicinity and send private messages.

- Sinatra
- PostareSQL
- Active Record
- Google Maps API



**FULL STACK WEB DEV** 

#### CONTACT

0478 416 800 adrian.mancuso@gmail.com linkedin: /adrian-mancuso/ github: adrianmancuso

### **TECH & LANGUAGES**

- HTML && CSS (including bootstrap)
- Javascript and several frameworks (jQuery, lodash, underscore.js, chart.js)
- Ruby && Ruby on Rails
- PostgreSQL
- Experience with AJAX requests and building an API

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# DEPARTMENT OF IMMIGRATION AND BORDER PROTECTION - MELBOURNE

#### FEB 2015 -JUNE 2017

APS4 Student Visa Processing Officer & Freedom of Information Officer

- Responsible for decisions and refusals on high risk visa applications with regard to relevant legislation
- -Worked collaboratively under the collective case management framework to reduce the Department's highest backlog to date.
- -Primarily worked on providing information for high-volume asylum seeker caseload

#### PRZYSTAN NA CHWILE- KRAKOW, POLAND APRIL 2014 - DECEMBER 2014

Arts and Events Coordinator

- Curated events, booked local and international talent for a riverside pop-up bar
- Responsible for organising successful opening weekend and associated promotion which over 700 people attended

## FREELANCE ENGLISH TEACHER-KRAKOW, POLAND OCTOBER 2012 - DECEMBER 2014

Responsible for wide, varied clientele from 6 year old children to actors practising for international roles.

#### **EDUCATION**

- 2017 General Assembly Web Development Immersive
- 2011 Victoria University Bachelor of Writing and Communication. Awarded the Fred Morton award for best graduating student in Communications